What is the biggest factors or traits that you
look for in people when you're building that company,
launching that venture? What is it that
you look for in people that you're like,
I need to bring him onto the team? So
people have certain just set things that they're great at.
So you can tell if they're a
sales type personality, an engineering, an operations type.
So that's who that person is. But at
the end of the day, you can teach skill,
you cannot teach traits. You cannot change who
that person is. So we look for a couple
different things that's super, super important that
are non-negotiables for me. I do not care
how talented you are. I don't care where you went
to school. I don't care if you knew someone at
the company and it's a referral. It doesn't matter to
me. You have to be coachable and you have to
be humble. So I don't care if you're the
most talented sales rep at XYZ company. That's amazing.
That's good. That tells me that you have talent,
but that doesn't mean that you're going to be
successful here. Are you coachable? Are
you humble? And are you persistent?